[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "You're a kind of fiery, emotional, soulful character, aren't you -- on and often stage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ":", "IN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "I'm just trying to live this interesting life we all have in front of us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "When you look at your extraordinary life professional and personal, how do you feel now about where you've arrived, where you are right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "I think at this point, I'm 51 now, I've realized, oh, it's just a journey.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "You're never actually going to arrive, are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "What's been the moment if I could replay it for you, you'd relive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Ooh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1994"], "ORGANIZATION": ["MTV"]}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "CD", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "When was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "That was 1994 unplugged, MTV.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Was it as good as you always hoped?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Yes, looking back on it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "That's the kind of music you want to get your little Chevy, get on the, you know, I don't know the Pacific Coast highway, get the shades on, ramp up the Etheridge, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ",", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Chevy"], "LOCATION": ["Pacific Coast"], "PERSON": ["Etheridge"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Properly in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "So, before you felt that you'd been in love, but you haven't been able to give that person the whole you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Well, I -- myself was, I felt owed; they'll fill this up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Have I cracked the Holy Grail of love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Terribly cheesy phrase, I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Because it's when you're the most searing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Well, it depends on how you look at it .", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Can you write good stuff if you're really happy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Can you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "-- from the artistry of your songwriting, if I said, write, you can be in this kind of existential state of pure bliss for the next 30 years, or torment, which would produce the better music, the better songs?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NN", ",", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "See, as you ask me that, this state of bliss you're talking about cannot exist without the other side, without the darker side.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "What would produce the better songs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "The contrast of misery, of course, is going to -- the contrast, that -- it's the desire to be out of that, into the bliss.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Or are you still thinking, you know what, a lot of talk, not enough action?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Having been on the journey of getting towards gay and lesbian rights, equality, understanding, diversity in America, 20 years ago, started the, you know, no, I was hoping in 10 years it would all be -- we'd all feel comfortable about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "But do you feel that the them that is you and those who are, again, lesbian like you, are in a much better position now that you have a president prepared to go on television and say, \"I support\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "WP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Is there more tolerance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Tolerance, you know, I don't even like to use the word tolerance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "What's the right word?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Because it sounds like, you know, I'm doing something that you have to tolerate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'60s"], "LOCATION": ["Kansas"]}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "But you feel it's getting better, even in states like Kansas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Especially Kansas, because I came from the Kansas in the '60s, which was the middle of the civil rights movement.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kansas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "And what do you think is the potential prospect of a Mitt Romney presidency?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "What -- is that linked to what you said to me, that basically you've learned to love yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "But do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Yes, you can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "What is the longest period you've ever had, where you literally couldn't write a song, of any quality at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Wow, well, I started writing when I was 10.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Do you get long blank periods, though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VB", "NNS", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Why did you feel that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "I was being a good grownup.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "If, God forbid, you were struck again by cancer, it came back or whatever, would you take marijuana?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "What do you want to be in five years' time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "I want to still be creating.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "What are you shaking your head for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I've had an interesting few days.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I feel that it is an unfair judgment and usually made from assumptions and from people who haven't read the book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "And if so, what is is the real Rielle Hunter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "I believe most people have the wrong idea about me, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rielle Hunter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "What do you think your public perception is right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Destroyer, villain, evil, basher.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "And how much of that is fair and how much of it is unfair, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "I think all of it is unfair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Edwards"]}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "For the public perception?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Well, the perception is based on a series of assumptions that you broke up John Edwards' marriage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "All of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "He is responsible for his career and his marriage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "What are you responsible for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "I'm responsible for my part in that, being the third party.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "I would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Do you think this is it, no?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "What is the truth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "It felt like the right thing at the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "What is the truth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "The truth is we've had problems for a very long time that we haven't addressed because we put the children first.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "JJS", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Are you surprised?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I'm -- what surprises me most is how mean people are and how much they judge based on things that they don't know anything about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "About me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Do you if it wasn't for his other children who have such strong feelings, particularly his oldest daughter who is obviously a fully fledged adult now who can make her own decisions, do you think if it wasn't for that and for their strong emotions about all this, you'd still be together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Does your gut feeling tell you that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "How can you say one event breaks up a relationship?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "Because you've broken up in the week that the book has come out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "You know, obviously -- did he read the book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "In my life, things happen all at once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Before publication?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "UNTER: Not before publication.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Did you offer it to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Many times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Why did he say no?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "You would have to ask him that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Why did he tell you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "He didn't want to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "He'd lived it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Did he try to stop you from writing it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "When did he read it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "You should talk to him about this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "So he has read the book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Well, I don't want to talk about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", ":"], "qSentId": 474, "question": "You won't talk about your book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "I want to talk about my -- yes, I do, but you can --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "What are the boundaries?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "The media is not entitled to everything in your life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Can you read it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Yes, I can read it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "You can?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Do you look back wistfully at those kind of clips and think, God, if only it could stayed like that, before anybody knew?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "No, I don't have those thoughts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Why were you smiling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Because it was fun, funny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Why does the media make everything so salacious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Because you put salacious material in your book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "ORGAN: Was it or wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Oh my God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Walked right into that one, didn't I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CD", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "You made no secret of it being the best sex of your life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Do they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "I never thought of it like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RP", ":", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBN", ",", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Who was the witch on wheels?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "I was talking about passive aggressive relationships, when a man doesn't stand up -- in general, relationships in general, when the man doesn't stand up, the woman is often seen as a witch on wheels, often vilified, which incidentally is exactly what has happened to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "But you were obviously referring to Elizabeth, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Elizabeth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Do you accept that when somebody is dead and can't answer back, it looks graceless?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "It accept it looks graceless, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "So you based everything in the book that you say about her on what John Edwards told you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "When you're in a relationship with a married man, that's how you're going to receive information about his marriage.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Edwards"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "You don't know if you can trust him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "I don't know if I trust him about everything that he said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Are you sorry for what you did to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "I am sorry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "If she was still alive, would you say to her I'm sorry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "Going back to that moment, what would you have done differently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "Oh, I never would have gone along with that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Why did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Out of fear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "True?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "Not true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "When you heard him and saw him do that, what went through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "I was devastated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "ORGAN: Why did he think he could get away with it, yeah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "I don't think he was in his right mind when he did that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "How did you find out, really know the truth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "John told me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "That must feel weird, doesn't it, watching that kind of clip?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "Yes, feels sad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "What goes through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "Nothing went through my mind, I just felt sad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "How could this end in anything but a catastrophic manner if this guy wants to be president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "That was a mistake.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "Whose idea was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "That was a mistake.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 711, "question": "Whose idea was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 712, "answer": "That was a mistake.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "What does it matter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "I'm curious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "So it was his idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "That was not true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "Whose idea was it not to use birth control?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "We were both adults.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "We were in love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "Like what were you both thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "We weren't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "At all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "Clearly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "You've been married before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "I have been married before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 742, "question": "You're a marriage wrecker?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 743, "answer": "UNTER: Yes, no, I understand marriage very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "I just think there's got to be a level of responsibility and self awareness, hasn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "There is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 766, "question": "Are you responsible at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 767, "answer": "I am not married.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 772, "question": "But you knew he was married?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 773, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "What has that been like on a human level?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "It's hard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 787, "question": "What are you responsible for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 788, "answer": "I'm responsible for the continuing on of the cover up in a big way and the continuation and the hurt and pain that came out of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "But you don't regret going to his hotel that night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "I don't regret loving him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 794, "question": "Yes, but you don't regret that action of yours, as a woman who knows he's a famous guy who's married, going to his hotel room for the night, which precipitated everything else, You don't regret that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBN", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 795, "answer": "I do regret.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 811, "question": "Given all of the publicity that the book has attracted, would you have written it a different way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 812, "answer": "I think that I would have edited a little differently.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 816, "question": "If John's kids are watching this, and they might well be, his daughter in particular, what would you say to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 817, "answer": "That I'm sorry for any pain that they've gone through.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "Genuinely sorry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 821, "question": "Are you more acutely aware, as she gets older, what you put them through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 822, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]